maui.net 2017-06-06

# Maui Net: Visitor Information For Your Maui Vacation | Maui.Net - All Things Maui

## Maui Net's Privacy Policy

**Revised January 2, 2007**

Maui.Net is owned and operated by Maui Global Communications Corporation, ( **"Maui.Net," "we," "us"** ). We provide travel information and services on our Web Site located at [http://www.maui.net](http://www.maui.net/) ( **"Web Site"** ). Maui.Net is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to our Web Site. 

This Privacy Policy governs your use of the Site, use of the services, and your receipt of Maui.Net's email newsletters. We respect the privacy of all those who visit our Web Site and use our services. We do collect online information from site visitors and our customers. Except as set forth within this Privacy Policy and in our [Terms of Service](http://www.maui.net/site-info/terms_of_use.php), we do not release personally identifiable information you provide us. Personally identifiable information includes information that can be attributed to a specific person, such as name, address, phone number, e-mail address or credit card information. 

This Privacy Policy covers the following areas: 

  * The information gathered through the Web Site 
  * The use of this information 
  * How you can change or remove your personal information 
  * Information about systems in place to protect your information 
  * Other issues regarding your privacy 

We review our privacy policy from time to time, and these items are subject to change. We ask that you bookmark and periodically review this page to ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our Privacy Policy. To contact us about privacy issues, to report a violation of our Privacy Policy or for any questions, please email us at support @ maui.net 

Internet Browsing 

We do not track any browsing by our connected customers. We do not see or save any activity even anonymous. Consequently, we do not sell any information to any third parties.

### Information We Gather

When browsing our site, you are not required to provide any personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, phone number or email address, unless and until such time as you choose to sign up for a service such as an email newsletter or contest, as described below. We do not collect any personally identifiable information from you unless you provide it to us voluntarily. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children (meaning minors younger than thirteen years of age). 

_Receiving Requested Email Messages_.  
You may choose to sign up for our feature emai l newsletters, which contain news of Maui.Net special offers and discounts. In order to receive the Maui.Net newsletters, you must provide us with your name, email address and your zip code. 

_Automatic Logging of Session Information_.  
We do automatically log technical inform ation about your computer's connection to the Internet, which we call "session information", that is anonymous and not linked to any personally identifiable information. Session information consists of things such as your IP address, operating system and browser software and the travel through the Site. Your IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the Internet, such as our web servers, know where to send you information such as the pages of the Web Site you wish to view. We collect viewers session information because it helps us analyze such thing as the way visitors are traveling through the Site, how many visitors are surfing to various pages on the Site, how long visitors to the Web Site are staying and how often they are visiting. It also helps us diagnose problems with our serve rs and lets us better our servers. Although such information does not identify any visitor personally, we can determine from an IP address a visitor's Internet Service Provider and the geographic location of his or her point of access. 

_Cookies_  
A "cookie" is a small file containing a unique series of numbers or letters that is placed on an Internet users' browser. One of the ways that we collect session information is through the use of cookies. We also use cookies for other technical reasons. Essentially, cookies are a visitor's identification for the Maui.Net computers, or the visitor's servers that placed them there. There is much misinformation circulating about cookies, but you should know that cookies are only read by the server that placed them, and are unable to do such things as run programs on your computer, plant viruses or obtain your personally identifiable information. Cookies allow us to serve you better and more efficiently, and to personalize your experience at Maui.Net's web site. By changing the options on your web browser or using certain software programs you can control how and whether cookies will be accepted by your web browser. However, doing so may disable some features on this and other web sites. 

_Blogs and Reviews_  
We cannot and do not control the acts of our customers or visitors. All customers and visitors should be aware that, when they disclose personally identifiable information in our reviews section or other areas on the Site, the information may be viewed and used by others to send that person unsolicited email. In the event that you encounter any person who you believe is improperly collecting or using information about you, please contact us. 

### How We Use (and Do Not Use) the Information We Gather

If you sign up to receive our Maui.Net newsletter, we use the personally identifiable information that you provided at sign up to personalize the email that we send you. Such emails are sent on infrequently, and they will clearly provide you with a method of cancelling, if you decide you no longer wish to receive them. In addition, we may on occasion send you an email regarding an important announcement or policy change that may affect you. 

_Non-personally Identifiable Information._  
We use non-personally identifiable information in a summary form to build higher quality, more useful online services by performing analyses of the collective characteristics and behavior of our customers and visitors, and by measuring demographics and interests regarding specific areas of the Site. We provide statistical information based on this data to suppliers, advertisers, affiliates and other current and potential business partners. We may also use the aggregate data to inform these third parties as to the number of people who have seen and clicked on links to their web sites. 

### Changing or Removing Personal Information

We retain your personally identifiable information so that we can provide you with meaningful customer service. If at any time you would like to have the rest of your personally identifiable information removed from Maui.Net's database, please contact us and we will use reasonable efforts to comply with your request. However, there will be technical information that remains in our databases, access logs and other records, which may or may not contain such personally identifiable information. This information will not be used for commercial purposes although we may, from time to time, communicate with former customers of Maui.Net. 

### Safeguards to Protect your Information

We take reasonable precautions to protect our customers' information from unauthorized third parties. When you are prompted by the Web Site to enter sensitive information (such as your credit card number), that information is encrypted with the industry-standard encryption technology known as Secure Socket Layer (SSL). While on a secure page, the lock icon on the bottom of web browsers such as Microsoft Internet Explorer or Netscape Navigator becomes locked. The servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment. However, no method of encryption or security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our servers, nor can we guarantee that information that customers supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted over the Internet. 

### Other Important Matters Regarding your Privacy

_Links to Other Web Sites_  
The Web Site contains links to other Internet web sites, including affiliated web sites that may or may not be owned or operated by us. We cannot and do not review all of the web sites that are linked to the Site, and we have no control over such sites. Unless otherwise explicitly stated, we are not responsible for the privacy or other practices of such sites, and the fact that we offer such links does not indicate any approval or endorsement of any material contained on any linked site. We are providing these links to you only as a convenience. Accordingly, we strongly encourage you to become familiar with the terms of use and practices of any linked site. 

_Promotions and Contests_  
If and when we sponsor promotions or contests, or third parties sponsor promotions or contests in conjunction with us, either we or the third party will post relevant privacy information in the official rules and/or registration area for the promotion or contests. That privacy information will govern that particular promotion or contest. 

**Special Note About Google Advertising**

Any advertisements served by Google, Inc., and affiliated companies may be controlled using cookies. These cookies allow Google to display ads based on your visits to this site and other sites that use Google advertising services. Learn how to opt out of Google's cookie usage. As mentioned above, any tracking done by Google through cookies and other mechanisms is subject to Google's own privacy policies. 

About Google advertising: What is the DoubleClick DART cookie? The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. When users visit an AdSense publisher’s website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user’s browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy [Google Privacy](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/privacy-policy.html)

_Other Permitted Release of Information_  
Notwithstanding anything in this Privacy Policy to the contrary, we reserve the right to release information contained within our access logs concerning any visitor or customer when that visitor or customer is in violation of our Terms of Service or other published guidelines, or engages (or is reasonably suspected of engaging) in any illegal activity, even without a subpoena, warrant or other court order, and to release such information in response to court and governmental orders, civil subpoenas, discovery requests and as otherwise required by law. We cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who may be using our servers or services for illegal activities. We also reserve the right to report any suspected illegal activity to law enforcement individuals or entities for investigation or prosecution. Please note that if we receive a formal request to disclose your personally identifiable information in connection with legal action, we will attempt to tell you about it before we respond to such request, if permitted by law, via the email address you provided to us.
